人人影視
原創翻譯  雙語字幕
字幕組招新中
請訪問 YYSubs.com
翻譯    蘇葵
校對    蘇葵
時間軸    江河
后期    漁夫
總監    蘇葵
寶貝  就想問問我們今晚是否如期進行
Hey, gorgeous, just checking that you're still on for tonight.
如果你需要我帶什么  告訴我
And if you need me to bring anything, let me know.
就這樣  拜
OK, bye.
寶貝  就想問問我們今晚是否如期進行
Hey, gorgeous, just checking that you're still on for tonight.
如果你需要我帶什么  告訴我
And if you need me to bring anything, let me know.
就這樣  拜
OK, bye.
寶貝  就想問問我們今晚是否如期進行
Hey, gorgeous, just checking that you're still on for tonight.
如果你需要我帶什么  告訴我
And if you need me to bring anything, let me know.
就這樣  拜
OK, bye.
偏遠郊區發現兩具男尸后
A murder enquiry has been launched after the bodies of two men
警方開始兇案偵查
were discovered at a remote farmhouse.
受害者的身份還未確定
The victims have not been formally identified,
但其中一人是現役警察
but one is understood to be a serving police officer.
警方還未就此案做出相關批捕
Police have yet to make an arrest in connection to the case.
這場殘忍的雙尸案發生于
The brutal double killing took place
昨日的康普頓馬丁附近
near Compton Martin yesterday.
想必大家都不會感到意外
You won't be surprised to learn that
這個案件已成為重大事件
this has been designated a major incident.
肖恩·哈達克督察被謀殺了
DI Sean Hardacre has been murdered.
我向你們保證
And I can assure you,
正如我剛才向肖恩的遺孀海倫保證的
as I've just assured Sean's widow Helen,
此案從今起成為我的頭等大事
that this will remain my first and foremost priority
直到我們抓到他的兇手并定罪
until we catch and convict his killer.
我知道你們和我一樣急切想找到這個混蛋
Now, I know you're all as keen as I am to nail this bastard,
所以我會調派我手下
so I will be seconding officers
不同隊伍的警察
from all the different teams under me
一起偵破這起案件
to work on this investigation.
就這樣
That's it.
工作吧
Let's get to work.
謝謝  長官
Thank you, sir.
你們可以用我的辦公室
You can use my office, you know.
那不安全
It's not safe.
上面有人在泄露消息
Someone up there is leaking information.
那我們要怎么辦
So, what are we going to do?
整天在這里鬼鬼祟祟嗎
Skulk around here all day?
你得在我們的調查外設立防火墻
You've got to throw a firewall around our investigation.
所以這現在是調查了嗎
So, it's an investigation now, is it?
伊茜給了我們足夠的線索進行調查
Issy's given us plenty to go on.
沒錯  但我們得不讓別人知道
Yeah, but we've got to keep that close,
只有我們三人
just between the three of us.
沒有證據顯示她的臥底身份被識破
There's no sign that her cover's been blown.
就給我們一點時間
Look, just give us some time.
看她能知道什么
See what she can find out.
伊茜是我們抓住肖恩兇手的最佳機會
Issy is our best chance of catching Sean's killer.
這不實際
It's not realistic.
為什么  只有我們知道她的存在
Why not? We're the only ones that know about her.
或與餐廳的聯系
Or the link to the restaurant.
凱恩像紅疹一樣鋪天蓋地地查這個案子
Kane is all over this like a rash.
我得告訴他
I have to tell him.
-不行  -他是我們的老大  漢娜
- No. - He's our boss, Hannah.
他也跟別人一樣
He could just as easily
可能是泄露信息的內鬼
be the source of the leak as anyone else.
你想要什么
So, what are you asking?
給我們一點空中掩護
Just give us some air cover.
確保我們不被
Just make sure that we're not
調派去主要事件偵查團隊
seconded to the major incident team.
如果我們找到任何線索  我們可以決定
If we dig up anything, then we can try and work out
在什么時候告訴什么人
who it's safe to tell and when.
這違反了所有規矩
This breaks every rule in the book.
那就讓我主導調查吧
Well, then, let me take the lead on it.
如果我們被抓包  你可以說
If we get rumbled, you can say
你讓我看看肖恩正在進行的調查
you asked me to take a look at Sean's ongoing investigations.
我從肖恩的文件發現了伊茜的存在
I found out about Issy through Sean's files
并開始利用她做我的線人
and I started running her as a confidential contact.
你都不知道有這么一號人
And you didn't even know that she existed.
好吧
All right.
給你們幾天  但必須時刻告訴我進展
You've got a few days, but I need to be kept updated.
我們所有人都在為此冒險
All our necks are now on the line.
在我們死之前
第二集
該死  我不行
Dammit, I can't!
聲音小點
Keep your voice down.
拜托  達沃
Come on, Davor.
去他的  別今天做
不是我的問題
Not my problem.
我買了籃球賽的門票
I have tickets for the basketball.
你會跟我去  對吧
You're coming with me, right?
不  我得學習
No. I have to study.
只是場愚蠢的游戲
It's just a stupid game.
但是四分之一決賽了
But it's the quarterfinals.
那你呢
What about you?
抱歉  伙計
Sorry, mate.
去你們的
Well, fuck you all!
成熟點  斯特凡
Grow up, Stefan.
-有什么問題  -你得去見安德里
那你呢
What about you?
我很忙
帶克里斯申一起
Take Christian.
別忘了那批貨
And don't forget the shipment.
媽的
Fuck!
臭死了  該死
It stinks. Shit.
-去他媽的  -我們在這干什么
- Fuck this. - What are we doing?
我才不碰那些玩意
I'm not touching that crap.
我們要找什么
What are we looking for?
大麻
Cannabis.
有多少
How much?
誰在乎  達沃可以自己玩蛋去了
Who cares, Davor can go fuck himself.
你不是那個意思
You don't mean that.
他一點不尊重我
He shows me no respect.
-去他媽的達沃  -來吧  斯特凡
- Fuck Davor. - Come on, Stefan. Please.
不
No.
今天有什么這么重要
So, what's so important today?
他非得讓你錯過籃球賽
That he's making you miss your basketball?
我們要去見安德里
We're supposed to meet Andri.
誰是安德里
Who's Andri?
一個阿爾巴尼亞瘋子
A crazy fucking Albanian.
安德里是我們進入卡拉布里亞的方法
Andri is our way into Calabria.
卡拉布里亞在哪
Where's Calabria?
你什么都不知道  對吧
You know nothing, do you?
那告訴我
So, teach me.
英格蘭半數的可卡因都從卡拉布里亞進口
Half the cocaine in England comes through Calabria.
好吧
Ok.
現在我懂了
Now I get it.
所以我們通過阿爾巴尼亞人進入卡拉布里亞
So, we go through Albania to get to Calabria
通過卡拉布里亞實現克拉伊納
and we go through Calabria to get to Krajina.
克拉伊納是什么
And what's Krajina?
與你無關
None of your fucking business.
克拉伊納是我們的過去
Krajina is our past.
也是我們的未來
And it's also our future.
我不明白
I don't understand.
你怎么會懂  你不是克羅地亞人
How could you, you're not Croatian.
我是混血
I'm half.
別擔心了
Don't worry about it.
只是達沃的愚蠢計劃
It's just some bullshit plan of Davor's.
他現在認為自己是大佬了
He thinks he's Mr Big Bollocks now.
說我們要掌管西南毒品交易的
Claims we're going to take over half the drug trade
半壁江山什么的
in south west or something.
什么  阿爾巴尼亞人會坐著讓給我們嗎
What? And the Albanians will just stand back and let us?
他說他們別無選擇
He says they won't have a choice.
來吧  我們離開這里
Come on, let's get out of here.
我們不能就這么走了
We can't just go.
他可以干自己的臟活
He can do his own dirty work.
克拉伊納是個巨大的
巨大的販賣可卡因行動
可能去見
可能去見安德里這人
今天
這里有多少
And how much is there?
大概五公斤
Maybe five kilos.
你得殺了魚才拿到嗎
And you had to gut the fish to get it?
并沒有殺魚  只是檢查每條魚體內
Well, not gut them exactly, just check inside each one.
有多少魚
And how many boxes of fish?
天知道
God knows.
很多
A lot.
我告訴你  克里斯申  有三百盒
I will tell you, Christian, there were 300 boxes.
然而斯特凡卻一整個下午都在外面喝酒
And yet Stefan was out drinking all afternoon.
我很榮幸跟一個正直的人做生意
You know, it is a pleasure to deal with someone with integrity.
這表達了我的感謝
This is a token of my appreciation.
謝謝
Thank you.
你現在跟我們混了
You're working with us now.
這是什么地方
What is this place?
是個安全屋
It's a safe house.
我不知道我們還用這些
Didn't know we still used those.
我們不用  是我用
We don't. I do.
一小時后見面
保齡
保齡球館
斯皮德韋爾
這是什么
What the hell is it?
前南斯拉夫的內戰中所犯的暴行
It's one of the few remaining photos of an atrocity that was
這是為數不多所剩余的照片
committed during the Civil War in the former Yugoslavia.
這告訴了我們
And it tells us everything
關于米密查一家我們需要知道的一切
that we need to know about the Mimicas.
經營那個餐廳的家族嗎
The family that run the restaurant?
他們在一個下午失去了
They lost more than 20 relatives and
20多個親戚和鄰居
neighbours in a single afternoon.
俘虜他們村莊的塞爾維亞人不分青紅皂白
The Serbs that captured their village were pretty indiscriminate.
你就要看到幸存者了
You're about to see the survivors.
這是杜布拉芙卡
So, this is Dubravka.
據我們所知  她是大家族的女族長
She's a bit of a clan matriarch, as far as we can tell.
這是她的妹夫  茲沃諾密爾
And this is her brother-in-law, Zvonomir.
他是我唯一之前交過手的人
He's the only one I've come across before.
我們有他的卷宗嗎
Do we have a file on him?
沒有
No.
他的名字出現在不久前的緝毒行動中
His name was linked to a drugs bust a while back.
局里讓我去進行審訊
The agency asked me to sit in on the interview
因為我在東歐的聯系
cos of the Eastern European connection,
但他沒被起訴
but he wasn't charged.
這是杜布拉芙卡的女兒  碧昂卡
This is Dubravka's daughter, Bianca.
她是伊茜嗎
Is she Issy?
說實話  我們不知道
The honest answer is, we don't know.
跟她牽手的人是誰
And whose hand is she holding?
斯特凡·瓦蓋奇
Stefan Vargic.
這是唯一一個我們手里有資料的人
The only one we have anything concrete on.
是什么
And what's that?
他做了18個月牢
He served 18 months...
蓄意持毒
For possession with intent.
這位杰出的男士是
And here's the illustrious man himself...
達沃·米密查  兒子和繼承人
..Davor Mimica, son and heir.
那是他男友嗎
Is that his boyfriend?
可能
Possibly.
家里其他人知道嗎
Do the rest of them know?
這些照片都是肖恩拍的嗎
And these are all taken by Sean?
他在拼湊事件前后
He was putting the pieces together.
肯定有人給他們通風報信了
Someone must have tipped them off.
發送
你在電話里說有新消息
You said on the phone that you had fresh information.
對
Aye.
伊茜給了新信息
Issy's come good.
說稍后會有一個會議
There's a meeting later on.
和這個人
With this guy.
安德里·卡巴夏
Andri Kabashi.
屬于阿爾巴尼亞黑幫  他們控制著南格洛斯特郡
Belongs to an Albanian gang that controls the coke trade
部分地區的可卡因販賣
in parts of South Gloucestershire.
這么說米密查打算擴張
So the Mimicas are looking to expand.
看來是如此
Seems that way.
-好  我得走了  -我也是
- All right, I've got to be going. - Yeah, me too.
比利  我需要拿回筆記本
Billy, I need that laptop back.
誰要
Who's asking for it?
芙蘭  但他們都提到了
Fran, but they've all mentioned it.
你能再給我幾天嗎
Well, can you give me a couple of days?
好
Ok.
你能錄音嗎
走吧
Let's go.
太危險了
達沃在哪
Where is Davor?
我替達沃說話
I speak for Davor.
聽著
Look...
我們只想讓你牽線搭橋
..All we're asking you is to make the connection.
如果你只有這個要求
If that's all you're asking...
那你自己牽線搭橋
..Then make it yourself.
但我們答應給你一大筆錢
But we are offering you a shitload.
我們給你25%的利潤
We give you 25% of the profit.
這是很大的讓步了
It's a big step up.
你為什么這么犯渾
Why are you being an asshole, huh?
那么
So...
我是個混蛋  是嗎
..I'm being an asshole, am I?
他不是這個意思  安德里
He doesn't mean that, Andri.
我們想成為朋友
We want to be friends.
對
Yeah...
朋友
..Friends...
不是敵人
..Not enemies.
我在這里  如果你需要幫助
發送
你要去哪
Where are you going?
尿尿
For a piss.
你要看嗎
You want to watch?
你在哪
回復
桌球室
克里斯申  克里斯申  你他媽在哪
Christian! Christian! Where the fuck are you?
克里斯申  警察來了
Christian, the police are here!
我們得走了
We have to go now!
快點
Come on!
"我是克里斯申  請留言"
"This is Christian. Say something."
克里斯申  你能給我回電嗎
Christian, will you call me, please?
好  慢點
OK, slow down.
沒人跟著我們  他們不是來抓我們的
There's no-one following. It's not us they're after.
我說了  慢點開
I said, take it easy!
媽的
Fuck!
他準備好交易了  一切都好
He's ready to deal. It's good!
一切都好  贊
All good. Yeah!
"我是克里斯申  請留言"
"This is Christian. Say something."
克里斯申  拜托
Christian, please...
漢娜
Hey, Hannah.
天吶
Jesus Christ!
克里斯申  他是...
Christian... He's...
他是...
..He's...
來個人幫忙  趕緊
Can I have some help here, people?!
別說話  呼吸
Don't speak, just breathe--
給她點空間  給她點空氣
Give her some room, give her some air!
怎么回事
警察來了
有人給他們消息了嗎
別擔心
肯定只是巧合
安德里一點也不小心
你覺得我們會有問題嗎
如果有  我們會知道
漢娜  三個未接來電
這怎么可能
How is this even possible?
我查了
I checked.
克里斯申和斯特凡·瓦蓋奇是獄友
Christian and Stefan Vargic were cell mates.
那肖恩呢
What about Sean?
他和克里斯申關系很好
He and Christian were close.
我聽漢娜說起過
I've heard Hannah talk about it.
他沒想過要告訴她嗎
And he didn't think to tell her?
我想他打算說的
I think he was going to, you know,
在她問了關于伊茜的事之后  但是
after she questioned him about Issy, but...
但他還沒來及說就死了
..But he never got the chance.
還有她去那干什么
What the hell was she even doing there?
她覺得自己能干什么
What did she think she could achieve?
我以為那是個年輕姑娘
Well, I was dealing with a young woman.
我擔心她
I was worried for her.
萬一她有什么麻煩  我可以去救她
I wanted to be there in case she got into trouble.
別對自己太嚴格了
Don't be too hard on yourself.
我
I've...
我讓他陷入了危險
..I've put him in danger.
這是他自找的
He brought that on himself.
我要叫停行動了
I'm going to pull the plug.
你能聯系他嗎  讓他退出
Can you contact him? Tell him he needs to get out.
這話還是由他媽媽說比較妥當吧
Wouldn't that be better coming from his mum?
漢娜根本不能辦這個案子
Hannah should be nowhere near this.
事情太復雜了
It's way too messy.
他不接我的電話
He's not answering my calls.
接著打
Keep trying.
這個太咸了嗎
Is this too salty?
這是什么
What is it?
帕斯蒂卡達燉牛肉
Pasticada.
很好吃
Oh, it's good.
-你個騙子  -抱歉
- You liar! - Oh! Sorry!
-真抱歉  你還好嗎  -嗯
- I'm so sorry! Are you OK? - Yeah.
不  給我看看  好紅
No, let me see! No, it's really red!
壞主意
Bad idea.
你有兩個手機嗎
You have two phones?
怎么了
What's going on?
我只是...
Oh, I was just, er...
手機掉了
..Dropped my phone.
有什么吃的嗎
Anything to eat?
帕斯蒂卡達燉牛肉
Ah, pasticada.
你能送一盤上來嗎
Can you send up a plate?
謝謝
Thanks.
我們都以為你只是
Oh! We were beginning to think you were
他想象中的人物了
a figment of his imagination.
你們約會多久了
How long have you been dating?
約會  不  天吶
Dating? No. Oh, my God!
這是我們約炮以后第三次見面
This is the third time I've seen him since we hooked up.
好好享受
Enjoy.
-他們喜歡你  放松  -我很放松
- They like you. Relax. - I am relaxed.
你想要什么
Do you want anything?
-你賣什么  -K粉  每包一百
- What are you selling? - Ketamine. Hundred a bag.
檢查一下
Check it.
-不值一半的價格  -你說什么
- They're not worth half that. - What'd you say?
便宜貨
Cheap shit!
我喜歡便宜貨
I love the cheap shit.
我給你便宜貨看看  基佬
I'll give you cheap shit, you fag!
給你  七十塊  給我滾
Here, 70 quid. Now get lost.
別這樣
Oh, come on...
玩會兒
..Have some fun.
-我不吸便宜貨  -放松  來吧  寶貝
- I don't do cheap shit. - Relax! Come on, baby!
干杯
Cheers.
你不用告訴我任何事
'You don't need to tell me anything.'
或許我該告訴你
'Maybe I do, actually.'
克里斯申
再叫我基佬看看  我諒你也不敢
Call me a fag again, I fuckin' dare you!
杜布拉芙卡給我們祝福了
Dubravka has given us her blessing.
恭喜你們
Oh! Congratulations!
你準備好派對了嗎
Are you ready to party?!
來來
Come, come, come.
我想敬大家一杯
Oh, I want to propose a toast.
等等  叫達沃過來
Ah, wait. Someone go get Davor.
他不會想錯過這一幕
He won't want to miss this.
你知道他在哪嗎
You know where he is?
在他辦公室
In his office.
他整個早上都沒來
He hasn't been all morning.
你今天跟他說過話了嗎
Have you spoken to him today?
我給他打了幾次電話  沒人接
I've tried him a few times. There's no answer.
或許他在開會
Maybe he's stuck in meetings.
誰是最后看到他的人
Who saw him last?
可能是我
Maybe I did.
他穿戴整齊準備出門
He was all dressed up to go out.
知道去哪嗎
Any idea where?
或跟誰一起
Or with who?
達沃總是一個人
Mm, Davor keeps himself to himself.
我可能知道他在哪
I might know where he is.
我可以去找找
Oh, well, I could follow it up.
但你不是家人
But you're not family.
或許這樣更好
Well, maybe that's for the best.
碧昂卡  把號碼發給他
Bianca, text him the number.
你一找到他  就聯系我們
The minute you find him, you call us.
明白嗎
Understand?
好
Sure.
帶上這個
Take this.
我不會需要  對吧
I won't need that, will I?
以防萬一
Just in case.
歡迎
Welcome.
謝謝你見我
Yeah, thanks for seeing me.
聽著  你在電話里說
Look, you said on the phone
達沃跟人打架了
Davor got into some kind of fight?
對  他跟販毒的吵架了
Yeah, he mouthed off to a dealer.
但你沒看到發生了什么  他們去了哪里
But you didn't see what happened? Where they went?
沒有  他就消失了
No, he just disappeared.
我找了他好久
I looked for him for ages.
你沒想過要聯系誰嗎
And you didn't think to call anyone?
誰  他母親嗎
Who? His mother?
好吧  那個販毒的是誰
All right, so who's this dealer?
高個子  長長的鷹鉤鼻
A tall guy, with a long hook nose
脖子上有紋身
and a tattoo on his neck.
你不知道名字什么的嗎
You don't have a name or anything?
我好像聽到別人叫他...
I think I heard someone call him...
馬特  對  應該是馬特
..Matt? Yeah, Matt, I think.
對  你認識他嗎
Yeah. You know him?
認識
Yeah.
打過交道
Our paths have crossed.
十分鐘
Ten minutes!
聽到沒  十分鐘
Oi? Ten minutes, mate.
不
No!
放開我  放開
Get off me... Get off!
別動
Don't move!
Don't fucking move!
留在那
Stay there.
你  滾出去
You, get out.
出去  趕緊滾
Get the fuck out now! Get out, now!
達沃  達沃  快來
Davor... Davor, come on.
快來  快  我們走
Come on. Come on, let's go.
我們得走了
We need to go now.
你在干什么
What the fuck are you doing?
你個混蛋
You fucking bastard!
停車  停...
Just stop, stop...
達沃  你還好嗎
Davor, you OK?
你還好嗎  達沃
You OK, Davor?
挺住  堅持住  達沃
Come on, stay with me, Davor.
你去哪了
Where have you been?
昨晚加班了
I had a late night.
我們很擔心
We were worried.
不需如此
You needn't be.
告訴克里斯申我要談談
Tell Christian I want a word.
你還好嗎  達沃
You OK, Davor?
你暫時不需要這身了
You won't be needing this for a while.
這是我的密碼  給自己買套西裝
Here's my pin. Buy yourself a suit.
我今晚有個重要的會議  你來開車
I have an important meeting tonight. You'll drive.
你現在給我工作了
You work for me now.
好
Ok.
克里斯申
Christian?
你從哪學會那樣拿槍的
Where did you learn to handle a gun like that?
《俠盜飛車》
Grand Theft Auto.
美式咖啡
Americano.
沒加糖
No sugar.
沒消息嗎
No word?
別擔心  他會聯系你的
Don't worry. He'll call.
我不那么確定
I wouldn't be so sure.
我不是克里斯申圣誕節賀卡上的頭號人物
I'm not exactly top of his Christmas card list.
他只需要時間消化這一切
He just needs time to process it.
決定他是否要繼續
Decide if he wants to continue.
他不能繼續了
There's no way he's continuing.
我想那由不得你
I'm not sure that's up to you.
我是他母親
I'm his mother.
對  但他是成年人
Aye, and he's a grown-up.
你聽到蒂娜說的了
You heard what Tina said.
如果她告訴凱恩  那整個團隊都知道了
If she tells Kane then the whole of HQ might as well know,
然后米密查家族的內鬼會...
and then whoever's leaking information to the Mimicas will...
他如果留下就是自殺
It'd be suicide for him to stay.
我來找你是為了提個其他建議
I'm meeting you to suggest an alternative.
讓蒂娜改變心意
Make Tina change her mind.
不如讓克里斯申做我的線人
Why don't I take over Christian as my contact?
你嗎
You?
我有更多回旋余地
I've way more leeway.
如果真的被人發現  我就說
If it ever came to light, I'd just say
我沒告訴你們倆他的身份
I kept his identity secret from both of you,
我不知道你們之間的關系
that I was unaware of the connection.
所以我不能參與嗎
So I wouldn't be involved?
你要參與
Oh, you'd be involved.
只是不是明面上
Just not officially.
如果他現在退出
If he pulls out now,
我們或許永遠抓不到肖恩的兇手了
we may never nail Sean's killer.
他是我兒子  比利
He's my son, Billy.
所以不要這一套"別問"的說辭
So none of this "Don't ask" Bollocks.
你要把發生的一切都告訴我
You keep me in the loop about fucking everything.
碧昂卡
Bianca?
碧昂卡  你在哪
Bianca, where are you?
我們得走了
We have to go.
克里斯申
準備好談談了
我早告訴你了
Told you so.
為什么選這里
Why here?
這里安全
It's safe.
我想他
I miss him.
我也是
Me too.
但如果他還沒死  我會因為
But if he wasn't already dead I'd bloody kill him
他把你卷入這一切而殺了他
for getting you involved in all this.
這是我的主意
It was my idea.
他應該阻止你
He should've stopped you.
他試過了
Yeah, he tried.
好吧  現在輪到我了
OK, so now it's my turn.
他們殺了他  克里斯申
They murdered him, Christian.
對  所以我們繼續調查
Yeah, and that's why we have to do this.
聽著  你需要知道一些事
Listen, you need to know something.
總部有個內鬼
There's a leak at headquarters.
米密查家族在警局安插了眼線
The Mimicas have got someone on the inside.
所以他們知道我了嗎
So they're onto me?
我想沒有
I-I don't think so.
你怎么能確定
Well, how can you be sure?
我不能
I can't.
但除了我  只有兩人知道你的存在
But there's only two other people who know about you.
你相信他們嗎
Do you trust them?
我最信任別人也就那樣了
As much as I can trust anyone.
其中一人是我的老板
One of them's my boss.
她想讓你退出
She wants to pull you out.
你不能說服她改變心意嗎
You can't persuade her not to?
我可以試試
I can try.
我要開車送達沃參加會議
I'm driving Davor to a meeting.
我看看是否有新消息
I'll see if anything comes of it
能幫助你改變心意
that might help change your mind.
這是錄音器
It's a recording device.
別你也來這套
Not you as well.
網上有五星好評
Had five-star reviews online.
你看著很像樣
You look the part.
來吧  我們走
Come on, let's go.
開始了
Here we go.
那是安德里·卡巴夏
That's Andri Kabashi.
另外一個人是誰
Who's the other guy?
我不知道
I don't know.
那是達沃·米密查
There's Davor Mimica.
你留在這
You stay here.
喂
Hello?
他沒拿
He didn't take it.
什么
What?
我該怎么辦
What do I do?
你去搞定
You fix it.
150公斤  這可是大量的可卡因
150kg - that's a lot of cocaine.
我們能搞定
We can handle it.
你會讓市場泛濫
You'll flood the market.
沒錯  并用低價逼退
Exactly, and price a lot of other people
其他的競爭對手
out of it in the process.
你這樣要樹敵
You're going to make enemies.
我干這行不是為了交朋友
I didn't get into this business to win friends.
而且這不是一次性交易嗎
And it isn't just a one-off?
這只是個開始
It's just a start.
這對我們雙方都會利潤豐厚
This is going to be very profitable for both of us.
150公斤
150 kilos?
他們要怎么出手這么多毒品
How in the name of God will they swing that?
我不知道
I've no idea.
這是個大證據  克里斯申
This is a hell of a lead, Christian.
現在留給我們吧
You can leave it with us now.
不
No.
不  我是認真的
No, I mean it.
你沒必要再深入虎穴了
There's no need to put yourself in any more danger.
但你們還是不知道他們要怎么操作
But you still don't know how they're gonna do this.
沒有我  你們永遠都不會知道
And without me you never will.
你不用證明什么
You've got nothing to prove.
給你的老板吧
Just give it to your boss.
告訴她還有更多
Tell her there's plenty more to come.
我跟你出去
I'll walk with you.
所以今后你就過來這邊  你保證嗎
So you'll come and go from here from now on, you promise me?
嗯  沒事
Yeah, it's fine.
比利是你的聯絡人
Billy will be your contact.
我參與此案會損害
My involvement would compromise
你提供的所有證據
any evidence you supply us with.
我明白
I understand.
但我會在這
But I'll be here.
還有  你能想個掩飾身份的說辭嗎
And, please, will you try and get some kind of cover story
萬一有人看到你進出這里
in case someone spots you coming in and out?
我很小心
I'm being careful.
還有  克里斯申
And... And, Christian?
我是認真的
I mean it.
你不用證明什么
You've got nothing to prove.